const quizDataFromFile = [
  {
    "question": "ben",
    "correct": "ich",
    "choices": [
      "sowieso",
      "Regisseur(in)",
      "ich",
      "selten"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "sen",
    "correct": "du",
    "choices": [
      "Zug",
      "du",
      "ab",
      "achtzig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "lütfen",
    "correct": "bitte (auffordernd)",
    "choices": [
      "früh",
      "bitte (auffordernd)",
      "Superlativpartikel",
      "Regisseur(in)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "öğretmen",
    "correct": "Lehrer(in)",
    "choices": [
      "ich",
      "fast",
      "Lehrer(in)",
      "bitte (auffordernd)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "tren",
    "correct": "Zug",
    "choices": [
      "bitte (auffordernd)",
      "Zug",
      "Regisseur(in)",
      "ab"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "seksen",
    "correct": "achtzig",
    "choices": [
      "achtzig",
      "Regisseur(in)",
      "fast",
      "du"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "en",
    "correct": "Superlativpartikel",
    "choices": [
      "selten",
      "Superlativpartikel",
      "manchmal",
      "achtzig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hemen",
    "correct": "gleich; sofort",
    "choices": [
      "ab",
      "gleich; sofort",
      "Zug",
      "ich"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "zaten",
    "correct": "sowieso",
    "choices": [
      "sowieso",
      "du",
      "ich",
      "bitte (auffordernd)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "-DEn itibaren",
    "correct": "ab",
    "choices": [
      "manchmal",
      "ab",
      "Zug",
      "Regisseur(in)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "bazen",
    "correct": "manchmal",
    "choices": [
      "ich",
      "du",
      "Regisseur(in)",
      "manchmal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "hemen hemen",
    "correct": "fast",
    "choices": [
      "ab",
      "ich",
      "selten",
      "fast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "yönetmen",
    "correct": "Regisseur(in)",
    "choices": [
      "Zug",
      "fast",
      "Regisseur(in)",
      "achtzig"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "erken",
    "correct": "früh",
    "choices": [
      "früh",
      "Zug",
      "ab",
      "Superlativpartikel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "nadiren",
    "correct": "selten",
    "choices": [
      "manchmal",
      "selten",
      "ab",
      "Superlativpartikel"
    ]
  }
];